Closet Monster is a drama, fantasy, mystery film directed by Stephen Dunn.
A creative and driven teenager is desperate to escape his hometown
and the haunting memories of his turbulent childhood.
Oscar Madly (18), played by Connor Jessup.
Peter Madly, played by Aaron Abrams.
Brin Madly, played by Joanne Kelly.
Wilder, played by Aliocha Schneider.
Gemma, played by Sofia Banzhaf.
Oscar Madly (9), played by Jack Fulton.
Closet Monster is a 2015 Canadian drama film
written and directed by Stephen Dunn.
It stars Connor Jessup as a closeted gay teenager, using elements of the
body horror genre as a metaphor for internalized homophobia.
It premiered at the Toronto International Film Festival, where
it won the award for Best Canadian Feature.
The film went into general theatrical release across Canada in July 2016.
The film explores themes of hamster, tree house,
rejection, bullying, newfoundland and labrador.
The tone is emotional and mind_bending.